Guide to the Stanford University, Haas Center for Public Service, Records SC0541
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1999-252
  - Information Files, Subseries 2
    - SIG 1987-88 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Stanford in Washington (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Stanford in Washington Council (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - School Long Range [re tutoring program] (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Tutoring/School Programs (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Tennis/Tutoring (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - TEAM (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - RSTP (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Center for a New Generation (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Ravenswood-Stanford Partnership (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - VAN (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - SVN 1988-89 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - SPOON (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Homelessness Bay Area (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Conference on Homelessness (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Staff/Faculty Service (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Environment (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Student Letters (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Style Sheet (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Summer of Service (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Summer Position (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Brochures (others) (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Undergraduate Major and Graduate School Information (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - General Records, Subseries 3
    - Affiliation Process (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Building: Blueprints (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Building: Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Building: New (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Building: Opening (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Building: T. Ford Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - California Compact (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - California Comprehensive Youth Service Conference (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Campus Compact Information on Federal Initiatives (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - COOL and Contacts at other Schools (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - City Year Program (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Conservation Core and Environmental Issues (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - East Palo Alto (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Ethnic Outreach (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Fellowships, Patricia Harris: Part 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Fellowships, Patricia Harris: Part 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Financial Aid (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Financial Aid: Assorted Applications and Brochures (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Financial Aid: US Senate documents 1979-1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Financial Disincentives: College Work Study (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Financial Disincentives: Education Research Group Proposal (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Financial Disincentives: Memo Proposals (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Financial Disincentives: Other School Programs (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Financial Disincentives: Survey Quotes (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Hayden, Tom- Docs Re: Cost of Education (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Legislation: Bill Lobbying efforts (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Legislation: Citizenship and National Service Act of 1989 Nunn (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Legislation: Federal Committees and Subcommittees (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Legislation: H. Con Res. GI Hawkins (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Legislation: House Education and Labor Committee (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Legislation: HR 460 Panetta (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Legislation: HR 1468.HR2225 Torricelli (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Legislation: HR 1479 McCurdy (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Legislation: HR 2156, 2157 Sikorski (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Legislation: HR 2632 Morella (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Legislation: S. 408 Mikulski (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Legislation: S 760 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Legislation: S.762 Pell (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Legislation: S. 1430 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Legislation: S.1731 Metzenbaum (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Manual: How to Survive at HAAS (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - National or Community Service (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - National Service Hearings: Hearing June 30, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - National Service Hearings: Hearing April 29, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Newsletters: Youth Service America (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Non-governmental legislation analyses and criteria (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Operation Civic Service (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Other College Programs (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Peace Corps: Legislative Reactions, Materials (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Points of Light Foundation (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Policy Paper: State of… (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Position Papers (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Public Service: Clippings (Box 7, Folder 8-10)
    - Ravenswood City School District, Projects with (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Registration Returned (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - San Jose Partnership (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Senior Fellows Program (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - SPONS: Articles (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - SPONS: Criteria, testimony and Xerox letters and notes (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - SPONS: Financial Disincentives Project, Disk 1989-90 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - SPONS: Legislation (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - SPONS: Pilot Program (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - SPONS: Responses / Recs H.R. 1430 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - SPONS: 1990 Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Stanford Project on National Service (Kim Grose) (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Stanford Survey 1989 Data and Analysis (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Stanford Youth Environmental Science Program (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Statistics on Student Involvement Fall 1989 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Volunteers in Asia (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Homeless Action Committee Records, Subseries 4
    - Binder A, 1990-1991: Bay Area Homeless Program (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Binder A, 1990-1991: Hewlett Grant (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Binder A, 1990-1991: Stanford Homeless Action Committee organizational materials (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Binder A, 1990-1991: Other Campus Groups (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Binder A, 1990-1991: Stanford Homeless Action Committee Sleepout in White Plaza (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Binder A, 1990-1991: Volunteer Info (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Binder A, 1990-1991: National Student Campaign Against Hunger and Homelessness (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Binder A, 1990-1991: Other College Groups (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Binder A, 1990-1991: Stanford Homeless Action Coalition Budget (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Binder A, 1990-1991: Community Groups Info (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Binder A, 1990-1991 Various Publications about Hunger and Homelessness Organizations (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Binder B: Stanford Homeless Action Coalition brochure, membership list (in front pouch of binder) (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Binder B: Minutes/Agendas for 1992 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Binder B: Coordinator/Director Info (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Binder B: Memo re: dorm presentations about homelessness (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Binder B: Campaign for a Fair Share (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Binder B: Campaign for a Fair Share (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Binder B: Campaign for a Fair Share (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Binder B: San Francisco Department of Social Services -- Analysis of Government Accountability and Taxpayer Protection Act (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Binder B: Blueprint for an Alternative State Budget (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Binder B: Newsletters of Hunger and Homelessness Coalitions (National, California, and San Mateo County) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Binder B: Statistics/Facts on Literacy (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Binder B: Campaign Information/Election Materials (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Binder B: Correspondence re: Gov. Wilson’s "Taxpayer Protection Act" (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Binder B: Article re: Riots and Welfare (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Binder C: Face the Music-Homelessness Awareness Through the Arts (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Binder C: Meeting Notes/Minutes (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Binder C: Possible Stanford Homeless Action Coalition Objectives/Projects (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Binder C: Meeting Notes/Minutes (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Binder C: Various Stanford Homeless Action Coalition applications (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Binder C: Stanford Homeless Action Coalition sheet, correspondence (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Binder D: Meeting Notes/Minutes/Agendas (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Binder D: Stanford Homeless Action Coalition organizational chart and information on members (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Binder D: Stanford Homeless Action Coalition minutes (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Binder D: Task Force -- Aggressive Panhandling (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Binder D: Task Force- Aggressive Panhandling (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Binder D: Field of Dreams Garden Project- Meeting Agenda (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - August 1994 Retreat (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Campus Presentations (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Text of Palo Alto Ordinance on obstruction of streets and sidewalks (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Student Activism Flyer (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Stanford Homeless Action Committee Contact Information (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Newsletter: Stanford Homeless Action Committee Sheet (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Stanford Homeless Action Committee Annual Report (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Special Fee Flyer (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Stanford Homeless Action Committee Promotional Pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Face the Music Promotional Flyers (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Palo Alto Weekly article on panhandling (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Administrative Committee Notes (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - 1993-1994 Roster/Applications (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Flyers (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - General Homelessness Information 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - National Student Groups (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Generic Haas Info 1994-1997 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Stanford Homeless Action Committee 1992-1993 Roster (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 1992-1996 Agenda and Minutes (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Stanford Homeless Action Committee Member Info (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Homeless Action Committee Publicity (Articles): 1994-1997 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Stanford Homeless Action Committee Publicity (Articles): 1994-1997 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Stanford Homeless Action Committee General Info (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 1993 COOL National Conference, Univ. Of Illinois, March 1993 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 10th National Conference on Student Communication Services- April 1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Manuals (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Homelessness Task Force 1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper Clippings: 1989-1994, Part 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper Clippings: 1989-1994, Part 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Master Copies (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Old Flyers/Sleep-out info (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Newsletters (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Displacement Forum Newsletter: 1986-1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Training Materials: Homeless Action Center: Feb. 6, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Press Releases (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Urban Ministry of Palo Alto 1990 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Theatre of the Homeless (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Studies on Homelessness and Poverty (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Stanford Homeless Action Coalition Advocacy (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Stanford Homeless Action Coalition Sheets Volume I-V (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Student Homeless Alliance -- Community Homeless Alliance (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Urban Ministry II: 1992-1996 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Articles: 1990, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - More Clippings: 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Stanford Homeless Action Coalition Palo Alto City Council (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Aggressive Panhandling Phone Survey (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Stanford Homeless Action Coalition Brochures (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Stanford Homeless Action Coalition Literature and Activity Information 1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Face the Music (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Visiting Mentor Program (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Mac-OS Disk "Tony Ciampi- Stanford Homeless Action Coalition" (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Audiovisual Materials, Subseries 5
    - Faculty Steering Committee 3/6/86 [audiocassette] (Box 14)
    - You Can Made a Difference: Families in Transition, Jan. 3, 1987 [master audio tape and 5 copies] (Box 14)
    - Kennedy-Cedro, undated [audiocassette] (Box 14)
    - Unidentified #1/2, 2/25/83 [audiocassette] (Box 14)
    - Unidentified #3, 2/25/84 [audiocassette] (Box 14)
    - Unidentified #3/4, 2/25/84 [audiocassette] (Box 14)
    - Laura Stuchinsky, Stanford University: "A Decision to Care" Mar. 14, 1987 [video reel; edited master] (Box 14)
    - Laura Stuchinsky, Stanford University: "A Decision to Care" Mar. 14, 1987 [audio tape] (Box 14)
    - Centennial #1 (introduction, Koppel meeting, different groups, etc) [H8 video tape] (Box 14)
    - Centennial #2 (Don Kennedy and Making a Difference album) [Hi8 video tape] (Box 14)
    - Centennial #3 (Panel discussion, John Gardner) [Hi8 video tape] (Box 14)
    - Stanford University Public Service Center "A Decision to Care", Sept. 7, 1987 [VHS; 4 professional copies] (Box 14)
    - Stanford University Public Service Center "A Decision to Care", early version marked "not for public viewing" [VHS tape] (Box 14)
    - Centennial event, Sept. 30, 1987 [VHS tape] (Box 14)
    - Upward Bound: Channel 7, May 23, 1991 [VHS tape] (Box 14)
    - Stanford University Hospital: Tribute to Peter Bing, undated [VHS tape] (Box 14)
    - Stanford in Washington, produced by George and Mary Lou Boone, undated. [VHS; 9 copies] (Box 14)
    - Paul Parkranger Mystery, Audobon Design Example, 1988 [VHS; Apple Computer Inc., - marked "in-house use only"] (Box 14)
    - Unlabelled VHS cassette, possibly blank (Box 14)
  - Restricted Materials, Subseries 6
    - Applications for the Kennedy Public Service Summer Fellowships (Box 15)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2000-165
  - You Can Make a Difference Records, Subseries 1
    - 1986 YCMAD Conference (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1987 YCMAD Conference (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1989 YCMAD Conference (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - YCMAD Conference Booklets 1987-92 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Haas Center Annual Reports, 1987-1994 and "A Century of Service: Celebrating our Commitment" 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Community Development Fellowship Program, Subseries 2
    - Local Government Internships Program (LGIP) 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Evaluations (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Publicity (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Penney Grant (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Guyer Fellowships (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Comm. Development Fellowship Applications (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Community Development Fellowship (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - CD '94 Applications (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - CD Evaluation Forms (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - '95 CD fellows (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Booklet: "Environmental Justice, Civic Organizing, and the National Park Service" by Esther Conrad (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - San Mateo info (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Files from Tim Stanton, Subseries 3
    - Strategic Planning (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - History (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Assistant Director/PR Development (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Files from Nadinne Cruz, Subseries 4
    - Evaluation/Statistics (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Budget Plans 1/17/92 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Three Year Plans (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Files, Subseries 5
    - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Orientation Materials, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Program 1987-88 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Clearinghouse Peer Advisor Orientation Materials 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - All-Haas gatherings materials for 1995-96 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Spotlight (newsletters) 1997-98 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Ravenswood Tutor Manuals, 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Booklets and Binders, Subseries 6
    - Stanford University Homelessness Proposal Project 1989 (Box 2)
    - The Homeless Veterans Resource Directory: A Comprehensive Guide to Bay Area Community Services 1990 (Box 2)
    - East Palo Alto/Stanford Summer Academy program report: summer/fall 1991 (Box 2)
    - The Bay Area Homelessness Program 1990 Annual Report (Box 2)
    - The Bay Area Homelessness Program 1992 Annual Report (Box 2)
    - The Bay Area Homelessness Program 1992-93 Annual Report (Box 2)
    - The Bay Area Homelessness Program Grant Proposal 1992-93 (Box 2)
    - The Stanford Homeless Project Hewlett/Campus Compact Grant 1991 Annual Report (Box 2)
  - New Haas Building Files, Subseries 7
    - Building: layout prints/plans (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Long-term plan furnishing (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Zone C maintenance (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Maintenance (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - In-House move (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Furniture Give-Away (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Snack machine (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Groundbreaking (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Opening (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Furnish (I) (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Furnish (II) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Furnish (III) (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Blinds (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Furniture wish list (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Furniture/equipment worth (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Directions/info on equipment (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - User Friendly (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - General Information (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Energy Conservation (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Environment (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Problems (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Plaques (for building) (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Landscaping (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Communications (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Move (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Betty meeting (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Site meetings (I) (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Site meetings (II) (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Meeting notes (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Layout plans for furniture (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Haas Public Service Center Project Manual, William Turnbull Associates, March 31, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Haas Public Service Center Project Manual, William Turnbull Associates, Dec. 19, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Haas Public Service Center Project Manual, William Turnbull Associates, Oct. 15, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Proposal for the Haas Center for Public Service, William Turnbull Associates, Architects and Planner, May 16, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Draft: Stanford University Haas Center for Public Service Building Project prepared by ROMA Design Group, April 1991 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Files on Service-learning: A Movement's Pioneers Reflect on Its Origins by Timothy K. Stnton, Dwight E. Giles, Jr., and Nadinne I. Cruz, Subseries 8
    - Learner's Guide (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - First draft – 34/5 Schools – Stroud Comments, March 1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Survey Drafts (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Survey – meetings, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Drafts of Report on Public Service & Higher Education Institutions (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Survey Returned questionnaires (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Draft of To Strengthen Service-Learning Policy and Practice: Stories from the Early Pioneers by Stanton, Giles and Cruz, Aug. 1996 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - To Strengthen Service-Learning Policy and Practice: Stories from the Field. Interim Report from a Service-Learning History Project, Aug. 1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Descriptive directories (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Survey / April meeting, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Survey of public service activity, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Returned surveys (Stanford/Waring), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Campus compact – Survey report program description June 1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Calls and messages regarding survey Feb. 1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Survey master list (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - PPCS Survey – original, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Contact information (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Contact information / Jeanne Halleck (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Blank surveys (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - John Duley, The Ever Present Possibility, March 1999 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Wingspread: archives video transfer notes (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Conference workshop materials (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - National Society of Internships and Experiential Education (NSIEE), publication, 1989-99 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Campus Compact: The Project for Public and Community Service (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - National Society of Internships and Experiential Education (NSIEE) Quarterly, Summer 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Synergist Publication – index 1971-1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Synergist 1980-82 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Experiential Education, a publication of the National Society of Internships and Experiential Education (NSIEE), 1979-87 (Sept.) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Experiential Education, a publication of the National Society of Internships and Experiential Education (NSIEE), 1987 (Nov.) – 1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Lisle (fellowship), 1945-96 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Lisle publication (fellowship), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Publications (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Merrill Field Program (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Campus Compact -- publications, 1989-94 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Audiovisual Materials, Subseries 9
    - Wingspread Conference Service-Learning, December 1995 [21 videocassette] (Box 6)
    - HPD Auction Sale Program, Breene Kerr Productions, Fall 1988 [videocassette] (Box 6)
    - New York City Urban Corps -- Michael Goldstein, founder of Urban Corps New York (1966), circa 1975 [videocassette copy of film in Box 8] (Box 6)
    - Audiotapes: Interviews dated 12/2 and 12/3/95 (Box 7)
      - Lou Albert (Box 7)
      - Herman Blake (Box 7)
      - Linda Crisholm (Box 7)
      - Dick Cone (Box 7)
      - Dick Couto (Box 7)
      - Nadinne Cruz (Box 7)
      - John Duley (Box 7)
      - Mary Edens (Box 7)
      - Dwight Giles (Box 7)
      - Mike Goldstein (Box 7)
      - Ira Harkavy (Box 7)
      - Jack Hasegawa (Box 7)
      - Gary Hesser (Box 7)
      - Fleda Mask Jackson (Box 7)
      - Jim Keith (Box 7)
      - Helen Lewis (Box 7)
      - LR: living room discussion, Tim's Group (Box 7)
      - Mezzanine Group (Dwight's group) (Box 7)
      - Sally Migliore (Box 7)
      - Bob Newbrough (Box 7)
      - Jane Permaul (Box 7)
      - Ken Reardon (Box 7)
      - Nancy Rhodes (Box 7)
      - Greg Ricks (Box 7)
      - Gib Robinson (Box 7)
      - Sharon Rubin (Box 7)
      - Joan Schine (Box 7)
      - Rob Shumer (Box 7)
      - Bob Sigmon (Box 7)
      - Tim Stanton (Box 7)
      - Marty Tillman (Box 7)
      - Jon Wagner (Box 7)
      - Michelle Whitham (Box 7)
      - Hal Woods (Box 7)
    - Julian Bond, "Status of Blacks/Race Relations/Service-Learning," 3/11/79 [audiotape] (Box 7)
    - To Strengthen Service-Learning Policy & Practice: Stories #1-#8, 12/2-12/4/95 [audiotape] (Box 7)
    - Wingspread Conference Service-Learning, various reels, 12/2-12/4/95 [audiotape] (Box 7)
    - Public presentation of students in Tim's Public Policy Class, late 1980s [audiotape] (Box 7)
    - HCPS Faculty Steering Committee, late 1980s [audiotape] (Box 7)
    - Staff Retreats #1-3, 1996 [audiotape] (Box 7)
    - Bill Ramsey, 1997 [audiotape] (Box 7)
    - Nick Royal #1 and 2, 8/18/97 [audiotape] (Box 7)
    - Judy Sorva Brown, 2/18/97 [audiotape] (Box 7)
    - Jim Feeney, undated [audiotape] (Box 7)
    - #1-#5: Tim, Nadinne and Dwight reflecting on book, undated [audiotape] (Box 7)
    - New York City Urban Corps – Michael Goldstein, founder of Urban Corps New York (1966), circa 1975 [film] (Box 8)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2001-237
  - General Files, Subseries 1
    - The Legacy of Public Service at Stanford University 1887-1994 – Honors thesis by Pipo Bui, 06/01/94 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Campus Report: Milton: Public Service Needs Serious Sustained Commitment 06/13/84 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Public Service Articles (interesting) 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Public Service Articles (1991?) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Public Service Articles (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Proposals at Inception (1984) (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Committee on the Stanford Community Service Center Proposal (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Public Service Center – The Statement (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Community Service Center: Application for Director and Assistant Directorship (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Early Development Materials - PSC (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Public Service Center background information packets (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Public Service Center Publicity 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 12)